Guide to the Samuel Rossiter Betts Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Samuel Rossiter Betts autograph collection
1704-1928
MS 603
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
(6 boxes)
Signatures of over five hundred famous Yale College graduates from the class of 1704 to the class of 1904. Also included is a small amount of Betts's personal papers including lists of his book donations to Yale University, an inventory of personal effects and other miscellaneous items. Arranged in three series.
Betts, Samuel Rossiter, 1854-1931
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The Samuel R. Betts Autograph Collection contains the signatures of over five hundred famous Yale graduates, as well as those of a few people not directly connected to Yale University. The items, which include correspondence and other papers, span the eighteenth through the twentieth centuries and are arranged in three series. Series I is arranged alphabetically by author. Series II includes one box of Betts's personal papers, consisting of a small amount of correspondence, writings, and lists of his personal effects. Series III contains additional autographs not listed in Series I.
Biographical / Historical
Born November 5, 1854, in New York City.
Died December 13, 1930, in New York City.
Father, George Frederic Betts (B.A. Williams 1844); studied at Harvard Law School; trustee of New York Institution for the Instruction of the Deaf and Dumb; Lieutenant Colonel of 9th New York Volunteers; son of Samuel Rossiter Betts (B.A. Williams 1806, LL.D. 1830) and Caroline Abigail (Dewey) Betts, of New York City. Mother, Ellen (Porter) Betts; daughter of the Rev. William Augustus Porter (B.A. Williams 1818) and Mary (Noble) Porter, of Williamstown, Mass. Yale relatives include the following cousins: John A. Porter (B.A. 1842), Frederic H. Betts, '64, and his sons, Louis F. H. Betts, '91, and W. Rosseter Betts, '98, C. Wyllys Betts, '67, Charles O. Day, '72, and his son, Charles O. Day, '03, James Hillhouse, '75, Charles B. Hillhouse, '78 S., and Francis Hillhouse, '79 S., and his son, Francis B. Hillhouse, '25.
Charlier School, New York City, and Mohegan Lake School. Two first prizes in English composition Sophomore year; oration appointments Junior and Senior years; Townsend Premium and first College Premium in English composition Senior year; second prize at junior Exhibition and speaker at Commencement; winner of quarter-mile run 1874; an editor of Yale Record and contributor to Yale Literary Magazine; Class historian four years; member Kappa Sigma Epsilon, Phi Theta Psi, Delta Kappa Epsilon, and Scroll and Key; elected graduate member Elizabethan Club 1919.
LL.B. Columbia 1877 and admitted to New York Bar; in law offices of Betts, Atterbury & Betts 1877-1880 (Frederic H. Betts and Charles L. Atterbury, both '64, and C. Wyllys Betts, '67, members of firm); member of firm of Briesen & Betts 1880-1884; associated in practice with his father 1884-1887; member of firm of Betts, Atterbury, Hyde & Betts 1887-1893, Betts, Hyde & Betts 1893-1897, Betts, Betts, Sheffield & Betts (James R. Sheffield, '87, and Louis F. H. Betts,'91, also members) 1897-1905, Betts, Sheffield & Betts 1905-1906, Betts, Sheffield, Bentley & Betts (Edward M. Bentley, '80, also member) 1906-1909, and Betts, Sheffield & Betts 1909-1911; counsel for Sheffield, Bentley & Betts and its successor, Sheffield & Betts, from 1911 until retirement in 1926; had specialized in patent and trade-mark law; counsel for numerous corporations, among them General Electric Company, Westinghouse Company, Edison Company, Automobile Association, Goodyear Manufacturing Company, Colgate & Company, Union Bag & Paper Company, and Hanan & Son; United States commissioner for Southern District of New York since 1877 and master in equity and examiner in United States Circuit Court since 1886; during World War advisory counsel to Alien Property Custodian of Bureau of Law and member of local Draft Board No. 112; a director of New York Institution for the Instruction of the Deaf and Dumb since 1898, secretary 1912-1919, vice-president 1919-1921, and president since 1921; member Republican finance committee, 25th New York Assembly District; contributed an article entitled "General Alumni Gifts to Yale" to Book of the Yale Pageant (1916); member Yale Bicentennial Committee and Alumni Board Committee on the University Library 1925-1930; on board of directors of Yale Alumni University Fund Association 1909-1926 (chairman 1913-1916); Alumni Fund agent for Class of 1875 since 1898; secretary of the Class since 1915; a governor of Yale Publishing Association 1922-1923; vice-chairman, New York District, Yale Endowment Campaign 1927; secretary of Yale Alumni Association of New York 1880-1883; member of council of Yale Club of New York 1903-1905 and of its library and arts committee 1902-1907 (chairman in 1904) and again since 1919; member of committee on admissions of University Club of New York 1892-1901; member American, New York State, New York County, and New York City Bar associations, American Association for the Advancement of Science, New York Academy of Sciences, Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York Botanical Garden, Society of the War of 1812, Society of Foreign Wars, Military Order of the Loyal Legion, the Pilgrims, and Grace Episcopal Church, New York; life member New York Zoological Society, American Museum of Natural History, Sons of the Revolution, and Society of Colonial Wars.
Married November 19, 1918, in Minneapolis, Minn., Lillias Verne Hill Armstrong, daughter of John William and Eugenie (Andros) Hill. No children. Mrs. Betts died May 31, 1929.
Death due to pneumonia. Buried in Woodlawn Cemetery, New York. Survived by two sisters, Mrs. T. Tileston Wells, of New York City, and Mrs. Amy B. Porter, the widow of John Addison Porter, '78. By the terms of his will his residuary estate was left to Yale University and $50,000 each to the Yale School of Law, the Yale School of the Fine Arts, and the Yale University Library; in 1923 he gave to the School of Law his complete file of several hundred volumes of patent and trade-mark cases with which he had been connected, and also his law library.
From Yale University Obituary Record.
Autographs; Betts, Samuel Rossiter, 1854-1931; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Autograph Collection, Series I
  Arrangement
  Records in this series are arranged alphabetically by last name.
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes autographs of Yale alumni. Dates in this series refer to the year of graduation from Yale University.
  - Adams, Andrew, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Richard, 1798 M.A. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams, William, 1827 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Andrews, George P., 1858 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archbald, R. W., 1871 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ashmun, George, 1823 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Atwater, Lyman, 1831 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Austin, Samuel, 1783 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Autographs: Folder 9 transferred to Series III, "Additional Autographs"
  - Backus, Charles, 1769 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bacon, Ezekiel, 1794 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bacon, Leonard, 1820 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bacon, Leonard W., 1850 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bacon, Theodore, 1853 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Badger, George E., 1813 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bail, Louis (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Baldwin, Abraham, 1772 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baldwin, Henry, 1797 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Baldwin, John D., 1839 Honorary (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Baldwin, Roger S., 1811 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Baldwin, Simeon, 1781 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Baldwin, Simeon E., 1861 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bannard, Otto T., 1876 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Barlow, Joel, 1778 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Barnard, F. A. P., 1828 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Barnard, Henry, 1830 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Battell, Robbins, 1839 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Beach, Abraham, 1757 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Beach, Lewis, 1856 Law (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Beard, Augustus F., 1857 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Beers, Henry A., 1869 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bellows, Henry W. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Benjamin, Judah P., ex-1829 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Berkeley, George (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Betts, C. Wyllys, 1867 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Betts, Frederic H., 1864 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bishop, William H., 1867 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bissell, Clark, 1806 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blackney, William A. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Blaine, Walker, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Blake, William P., 1852 S (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bliss, William, 1825 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Boies, Henry M., 1859 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Booth, David, 1819 M.A. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bouton, Nathaniel, 1821 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bowen, Jabez, 1757 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Brace, Charles L., 1846 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Brainerd, John, 1746 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Brewster, Chauncey B., 1868 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Brinton, Daniel G., 1858 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bristed, Charles A., 1839 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Brooks, Phillips (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Brown, Addison (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Brown, B. Gratz, 1847 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Brown, Henry A., 1865 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Brown, Henry B., 1856 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Brown, John M., 1856 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Brown, Joseph E., 1846 Law (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Brown, Robert, 1857 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Brown, William A., 1886 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Brownson, Nathan, 1761 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bruce, Wallace, 1867 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Buckingham, William A., 1866 Honorary (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Burnside, A E (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Burr, Joseph A., 1871 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bushnell, Horace, 1827 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Calhoun, John C., 1804 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Calhoun, William B., 1814 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Camp, Walter, 1880 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Carrington, Edward (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Carrington, Henry B., 1845 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Carter, Leslie, 1873 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Chamberlain, D H, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Chapin, Calvin, 1788 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Chase, George, 1870 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Chester, John, 1766 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Child, Calvin G., 1855 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Chipman, Nathaniel, 1777 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Chittenden, Russell H., 1875 S (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Clark, Thomas M., 1831 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Clay, Cassius M., 1832 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Cleaveland, Moses, 1777 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Coit, Thomas W., 1821 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Coleman, Lyman, 1817 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Collier, M. Dwight, 1866 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Colton, George H., 1840 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Cook, Joseph, ex- (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Cooke, Joseph P., 1750 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Cooper, James Fenimore, ex- (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Corbyn, William B., 1839 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Cornelius, Elias, 1813 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Cox, Christopher C., 1835 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Crapo, William W., 1852 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Cushing, Caleb (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Cushing, Harvey, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Cutler, Manasseh, 1765 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Cutler, Timothy (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Cuyler, Thomas DeWitt, 1874 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Daggett, Naphtali, 1748 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Dalzell, John, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Dana, Edward S., 1870 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Dana, James D., 1833 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Dana, Samuel W., 1775 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Davenport, Abraham, 1732 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Davenport, James, 1732 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Davenport, James, 1777 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Davies, Thomas F., 1853 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Davis, Henry, 1796 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Davis, John, 1812 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Dawes, Henry L., 1839 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Day, George E., 1833 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Day, George Parmly, 1897 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Day, Jeremiah, 1795 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Day, Thomas, 1797 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Dean, Gilbert, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Deane, Silas, 1785 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - DeForest, Robert W., 1870 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - deKay, Charles, 1868 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Delafield, Edward, 1812 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Delancey, William H., 1817 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Depew, Chauncey M., 1856 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Dewey, Orrville (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Dexter, Franklin B., 1861 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Dexter, Henry M., 1840 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Dickinson, John D., 1785 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Douglass, David B., 1813 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Dubois, Fred T., 1872 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Dummer, Jeremiah (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Duncan, Alexander, 1825 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Duncan, Garnett, 1820 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Dutton, Henry, 1818 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Dwight, Sereno E., 1803 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Dwight, Theodore W., 1892 Honorary (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Dwight, Timothy, 1769, 1849 (Box 2, Folder 133-134)
  - Dyer, Eliphalet, 1740 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Eaton, Daniel C., 1857 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Edwards, Jonathan, 1720, 1819 (Box 2, Folder 137-138)
  - Eld, Edward (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Elliott, John, 1786 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Ellsworth, Henry L., 1820 (Box 2, Folder 140A)
  - Ellsworth, Oliver, 1790 Honorary (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Ellsworth, William W., 1810 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Farnam, Henry, 1871 Honorary (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Farnam, William W., 1866 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Ferry, Orris S., 1844 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Field, David S., 1802 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Field, Stephen (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Finch, Francis M., 1849 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Fisher, Alex M., 1813 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Fisher, George P., 1867 Honorary (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Fiske, Phineas, 1704 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Fitch, Eleazar, 1743 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Fitch, Lucius W., 1840 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Fitch, Thomas, 1721 (Box 2, Folder 153A)
  - Foot, Samuel A., 1797 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Foster, Dwight, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Fowler, Orin, 1815 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Franklin, Thomas E. (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Frissell, Hollis B., 1874 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Frothingham, O B (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Gallaudet, Thomas H., 1805 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Gibbs, Josiah W., 1809 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Gibson, Randall L., 1853 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Gillett, Ezra H., 1841 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Gold, Thomas R., 1786 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey, 1776 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey A., 1810 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Goodrich, Elizur, 1779 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Goodyear, William H., 1867 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Granger, Francis, 1811 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Griffin, Edward D., 1790 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Grimke, Thomas S., 1807 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Griswold, Matthew, 1779 Honorary (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Griswold, Roger, 1780 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Grosvenor, Thomas, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Hadley, Arthur T., 1876 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Hadley, James, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Haldeman, Richard J., 1851 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Hall, Lyman, 1747 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Hall, Willard P., 1839 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Hall, Willis, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Hammond, John Hays, 1876 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Harris, William T., 1858 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Harrison, Burton N., 1859 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Harrison, Carter H., 1845 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Hawes, Joel, 1846-1867 Fellow (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Hawley, Joseph, 1742 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Higgins, Anthony, 1861 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Hillhouse, James, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Hillhouse, James A., 1749, 1808 (Box 2, Folder 190-191)
  - Hillhouse, William, 1777 (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Hitchcock, Edward, 1818 Honorary (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Hitchcock, H L, 1832 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Hitchcock, Peter, 1801 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Hitchcock, Samuel J., 1809 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Hobart, John S., 1757 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Holley, Horace, 1803 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - Hollister, Howard C., 1878 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Holmes, Abiel, 1783 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - Holt, George C., 1866 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - Holt, Henry, 1862 (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - Hopkins, Mark (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - Hopkins, Samuel, 1741 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - Hopkins, Samuel M., 1731 (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - Hoppin, James M., 1840 (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - Hosmer, Titus, 1757 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - Hoyt, Henry M., 1878 (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - Hubbard, Richard D., 1839 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Hubbard, Samuel, 1802 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Hubbard, Thomas H., 1799 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Hull, William, 1772 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Humphrey, David, 1771 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Humphrey, Herman, 1805 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Huntington, Benjamin, 1761 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Huntington, Ebenezer, 1775 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Huntington, Jabez W., 1806 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Huntington, Samuel, 1779 Honorary, 1785 (Box 3, Folder 219-220)
  - Huntington, Simon, 1741 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Ingersoll, Jared, 1742, 1766 (Box 3, Folder 222-223)
  - Ingersoll, Jonathan, 1766 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph I., 1808 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Irving, Washington (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Ives, Brayton, 1861 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Jackson, Henry R., 1839 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Jackson, Joseph C., 1857 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Jarvis, Samuel F., 1805 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Jay, William, 1807 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Jenks, Almet F., 1875 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Johnson, Alexander S., 1835 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Johnson, Samuel, 1714 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Johnson, Samuel W., 1857 Honorary (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Johnson, William, 1788 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Johnson, William S., 1744 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Johnston, William P., 1852 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Jordon, David S. (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Judd, Albert F., 1862 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Kane, John K., 1814 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Kean, John, 1876 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Keasbey, Anthony Q., 1843 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Kellogg, Stephen W., 1846 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Kent, James, 1781 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1904 M.A. (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Kernochan, Frank E., 1861 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Keyes, Edward L., 1863 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - King, Clarence, 1862 S (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Kingsbury, Frederick J., 1846 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Kinglsey, Henry C., 1834 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Kinglsey, James L., 1799 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Kinglsey, William L., 1843 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Kip, William I., 1831 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Kirkland, Joseph, 1790 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Kirtland, Jared P., 1815 M.A. (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Knight, Jonathan, 1808 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Lanman, James, 1788 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Lathrop, Gardiner, 1869 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Lathrop, Joseph, 1754 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Law, Richard, 1751 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Learned, William Law, 1841 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Leavenworth, Elias W., 1824 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Leavitt, Joshua, 1814 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Lewis, Charlton T., 1853 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Lines, Edwin S., 1872 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Livingston, John, 1733 (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - Livingston, John H., 1762 (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Livingston, Peter Van Brugh, 1731 (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Livingston, Philip, 1737 (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - Livingston, William, 1741 (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - Locke, John, 1819 (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - Loomis, Elias, 1830 (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - Lord, George D., 1854 (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Lovett, John, 1782 (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Lyman, Hart, 1873 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - Lyman, Joseph, 1767, 1783 (Box 3, Folder 277-278)
  - Lyman, Phineas, 1738 (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - Lyman, William, 1776 (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - Lynde, William P., 1838 (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - McClung, Thomas Lee, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - McCurdy, Charles J., 1817 (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - McDermott, Charles, 1828 (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - MacVeagh, Franklin, 1862 (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - MacVeagh, Wayne, 1853 (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - Mallery, Garrick, 1850 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - Mansfield, Jared, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - March, Daniel, 1840 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - Marsh, Othniel, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - Mason, Edward G., 1860 (Box 3, Folder 291)
  - Mason, Jeremiah, 1788 (Box 3, Folder 292)
  - Mason, Lowell (Box 3, Folder 293)
  - Masters, Josiah, 1785 (Box 3, Folder 294)
  - Mathews, Albert, 1842 (Box 3, Folder 295)
  - Meigs, Henry, 1799 (Box 3, Folder 296)
  - Meigs, Josiah, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 297)
  - Meigs, R J, 1785 (Box 3, Folder 298)
  - Merrill, Payson, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 299)
  - Merritt, Schuyler, 1873 (Box 3, Folder 300)
  - Miller, George D., 1870 (Box 3, Folder 301)
  - Minor, William T., 1834 (Box 3, Folder 302)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 303)
  - Mitchell, Donald G., 1841 (Box 3, Folder 304)
  - Mitchell, Stephen M., 1763 (Box 3, Folder 305)
  - Moore, Robert, 1805 (Box 3, Folder 306)
  - Morgan, Christopher, 1828 (Box 3, Folder 307)
  - Morris, Lewis, 1746 (Box 3, Folder 308)
  - Morris, Richard, 1748 (Box 3, Folder 309)
  - Morse, Richard C., 1862 (Box 3, Folder 310)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B., 1810 (Box 3, Folder 311)
  - Morse, Sidney E., 1811 (Box 3, Folder 312)
  - Morton, S G (Box 3, Folder 313)
  - Mosely, William A., 1816 (Box 3, Folder 314)
  - Mumford, Paul, 1754 (Box 3, Folder 315)
  - Murray, William H. H., 1862 (Box 3, Folder 316)
  - Nelson, S (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Newton, Hubert A., 1850 (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Nichols, Starr H., 1854 (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Nickerson, Sereno D., 1845 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Nicollet, Joseph N. (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Noble, John W., 1851 (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - North, Simeon, 1825 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Nott, Elipht (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Olcott, Simeon E., 1761 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Owen, Allen F., 1837 (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Packard, Lewis R., 1856 (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Palmer, Ray, 1830 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Parker, Joel (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Parker, Peter, 1831 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Parsons, Herbert, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - Parsons, Theophilus (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Partridge, Sidney C., 1880 (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Patton, John, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Paulding, Hiram (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Payne, Oliver H., 1863 (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Peabody, George (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Percival, James G., 1815 (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Perkins, Samuel C., 1848 (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Peters, John A., 1842 (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Peters, Samuel, 1757 (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Phelps, Edward J., 1881 Honorary (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Phelps, Elisha, 1800 (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Phelps, Samuel S., 1811 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - Phelps, William Watter, 1860 (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - Pierpont, John, 1804 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - Pigott, James P., 1878 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, 1889 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - Pitkin, Timothy, 1785 (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - Platt, Thomas C., 1853 (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - Polk, Frank L., 1894 (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - Polk, Trusten, 1831 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - Poole, William F., 1849 (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - Porter, John A., 1842, 1878 (Box 4, Folder 354-355)
  - Porter, Noah, 1831 (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Porter, Peter B., 1791 (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Powell, J W (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - Putnam, James O., 1839 (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Pynchon, Joseph, 1757 (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Reed, John, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - Remington, Frederic, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - Richards, Charles, 1849 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - Richards, William R., 1875 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - Robbins, Asher, 1782 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - Roberts, Ellis H., 1850 (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - Robinson, Henry C., 1853 (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - Rockwell, Julius, 1826 (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1901 Honorary (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - Ruggles, Samuel B., 1814 (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - Ruskin, John (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Salisbury, Edward E., 1832 (Box 4, Folder 372)